<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <secciones>	<lang value="es">  		<titulo>Pato</titulo>		<boton1>QUIÉN SOY</boton1>		<carga_boton1>characters/pato_info.swf</carga_boton1>		<boton2>ACTIVIDADES</boton2>		<carga_boton2>characters/activities/activities.swf</carga_boton2>		<texto>Pato es el mejor amigo de Pocoyo. Es un tipo fiel, noble y muy pulcro. La suciedad le espanta, tiene vértigo y todo lo nuevo le asusta. Aunque al lado del intrépido Pocoyo, su prudencia le sirve de poco.</texto>	</lang>	<lang value="en">  		<titulo>Pato</titulo>		<boton1>ABOUT ME</boton1>		<carga_boton1>characters/pato_info.swf</carga_boton1>		<boton2>ACTIVITIES</boton2>		<carga_boton2>characters/activities/activities.swf</carga_boton2>				<texto>Pocoyo’s good friend Pato is the kind of duck who likes things “just so”.He’s very cautious – in fact, you might say he was a little too uptight for his own good. But, for all his caution and planning,  things never seem to turn out the way he wants them to.</texto>	</lang>	<lang value="fr">  		<titulo>Pato</titulo>		<boton1>QUI SUIS-JE</boton1>		<carga_boton1>characters/pato_info.swf</carga_boton1>		<boton2>ACTIVITÉS</boton2>		<carga_boton2>characters/activities/activities.swf</carga_boton2>		<texto>Le grand ami de Pocoyo, Pato, est un canard qui aime les choses bien faitesIl est très prudent, d’ailleurs, on pourrait dire que parfois il est un peu maniaque. Mais, malgré toutes ses précautions et tous ses plans, les choses ne vont jamais comme il les a prévues.</texto>	</lang>		<lang value="it">  		<titulo>Pato</titulo>		<boton1>SU DI ME</boton1>		<carga_boton1>characters/pato_info.swf</carga_boton1>		<boton2>ATTIVITÀ</boton2>		<carga_boton2>characters/activities/activities.swf</carga_boton2>		<texto>Pato, il grande amico di Pocoyo, è un tipo a cui piace riflettere sulle cose. È molto cauto, ma forse dovrebbe prendersi le cose un po’ meno sul serio, anche perché, nonostante la sua calma e i suoi ragionamenti, le cose non vanno mai a finire come vorrebbe lui.</texto>	</lang>		<lang value="po">  		<titulo>Pato</titulo>		<boton1>SOBRE MIM</boton1>		<carga_boton1>characters/pato_info.swf</carga_boton1>		<boton2>ATIVIDADES</boton2>		<carga_boton2>characters/activities/activities.swf</carga_boton2>		<texto>O bom amigo de Pocoyo é um pato que gosta das coisas bem feitas. É muito precavido: de facto, há quem diga que é um pouco preocupado demais com tudo. Porém, apesar de todas as suas precauções e planos, as coisas nunca parecem resolver-se como ele quer.</texto>	</lang>		<lang value="de">  		<titulo>Pato</titulo>		<boton1>ÜBER MICH</boton1>		<carga_boton1>characters/pato_info.swf</carga_boton1>		<boton2>TÄTIGKEITEN</boton2>		<carga_boton2>characters/activities/activities.swf</carga_boton2>		<texto>Pocoyo's bester Freund ist Pato. Ein Typ von Ente, der die gut gelungenen Dinge gefallen. Er ist sehr umsichtig und manchmal sogar etwas sonderlich, könnte man sagen. Das Problem ist, dass trotz seiner Umsicht und Planung die Dinge nie so ausgehen, wie er es geplant hat.</texto>	</lang>				</secciones>